So we also have the AI chat item over here.
So it is probably something very similar
to what we have with the chatbots, right?
So this is the chatbot part of Quillbot probably.
So it says how can I help you need help
with brainstorming as you see?
It's very similar.
It's actually exactly another random chatbot out there, right?
And it's also included in the Quillbot tools.
So as you see, I can ask it anything.
So I can say, as you see, it even has its own suggestions.
So brainstorm ideas, generate a product description,
interview questions, review my resume, et cetera.
We also have web search item option.
And we also can click upload files to actually upload files.